A Wish for Christmas is a tv movie, romance, drama
film directed by Christie Will Wolf.
Sara Shaw is the type of woman who prefers to sit on the sidelines at work, but when her big idea for a Christmas
initiative is stolen, she makes a wish to Santa that she'll finally have the courage to stand up for herself.
Santa grants her wish, but only gives her 48 hours.
As the clock ticks, Sara will discover how to channel the
Christmas magic and speak her mind all on her own.
Sara Shaw, played by Lacey Chabert.
Peter Williams, played by Paul Greene.
Molly, played by Andrea Brooks.
Barb, played by Colleen Wheeler.
Aunt Lizzie, played by Kendall Cross.
Mr. Williams, played by Michael Ryan.
A Cinderella Story: Christmas Wish is a 2019 American musical teen comedy written and
directed by Michelle Johnston and starring Laura Marano and Gregg Sulkin.
It is the fifth installment of the A Cinderella Story film series.
The film was released digitally on October 15,
2019, and DVD on October 29, 2019.
Its stand-alone sequel, A Cinderella Story: Starstruck, was released in 2021.
The film explores themes of work, holiday, boss, wish, christmas.
The tone is emotional.